

I am currently doing a Master's degree in Interaction Design at Aalborg Univeristy (AAU). I am curious about technology, analytically inclined, and I enjoy being challenged and developing new skills.

I am looking for a job as an Interaction Designer or UI/UX Designer. I have a wide field of interest in design including user research, ideation, prototyping, and implementation.

For the past 3 years I have worked as a gymnastics instructor at DGI-Huset Nordkraft where I teach kids to do flips. Beyond that I have worked as an assistant teacher at AAU for the course "Imperative Programming in C".

FULL NAME:

Lasse Hjort

DATE OF BIRTH:

May 30, 1997

EDUCATION

Master's Student in Interaction Design at Aalborg University

SKILLS

Through my education I have acquired a deep understanding of many different aspects of Interaction Design such as:

- User-Centered Design
- Participatory Design
- Usability Testing
- Prototyping
- UX Research (Qualitative and Quantitative)

I also have experience with different programming languages including:

- HTML
- CSS
- C (Imperative)
- C# (Object-oriented)
- Java (Android)
- JavaScript



Timeline

Education

Master's Degree in Interaction Design

September 2021 - June 2023

Aalborg University (AAU)

I am currently working on a Master thesis about domestic electricity consumption in collaboration with NRGi.

Bachelor's Degree in Interaction Design

September 2018 - June 2021

Aalborg University (AAU)

My Bachelor thesis was done in collaboration with Aalborg Univeristy Library and was about designing an interactive map to help students find a suitable spot to study at the library. More info about this project can be found in my portfolio.

Work Experience

Gymnastics Instructor

April 2019 - Present

DGI-Huset Nordkraft

I teach gymnastics to kids aged 6-15 years old on DGI-Huset Nordkraft's Kidfit teams. I also facilitate events where kids come to play on the trampolines and the rest of the equipment.

Assistant Teacher

September 2020 -December 2020

AAU "Imperative Programming in C"

I took this course as part of my education and a year later I was invited to become an assistant teacher for the course. After each lecture I was responsible for helping the students understand and complete assignments related to the course.